<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<kiln:root xmlns:i18n="http://apache.org/cocoon/i18n/2.1"
           xmlns:kiln="http://www.kcl.ac.uk/artshums/depts/ddh/kiln/ns/1.0"
           xmlns:xi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XInclude"
           xmlns:xsl="http://www.w3.org/1999/XSL/Transform">

  <kiln:parent>
    <xi:include href="base.xml" />
  </kiln:parent>

  <kiln:child>
    <kiln:block name="title">
      <i18n:text>SigiDoc: Home</i18n:text>
    </kiln:block>

    <kiln:block name="page-header">
      <div class="row">
        <div class="large-12 columns text-center">
          <h1>
            <!--<span class="round label">-->
            <i18n:text i18n:key="home-title">SigiDoc 1.0: a sample corpus</i18n:text>
            <!--</span>-->
          </h1>
        </div>
      </div>
    </kiln:block>

    <kiln:block name="content-section">
      <main>
        <div class="row">
          <div class="large-12 columns">
            <div class="panel radius">
              <p>Seals are the only remnants of the written documents used for daily administration
                and private correspondence from the 4th to the 15th C. in the Byzantine Empire – i.e.
                the Christian eastern medieval empire centred upon Constantinople – whose public and
                private archives are nearly entirely lost. As such seals do not supplement archival
                material but have to substitute it, which explains the unique importance of
                sigillography for Byzantine studies.</p>
            </div>
          </div>
          <div class="large-12 columns">
            <div class="panel radius">
              <p>SigiDoc provides XML-based and TEI-compliant encoding standards for the description
                and edition of Byzantine seals: as such, it aims to establish a set of rules and
                guidelines to publish Byzantine seals in digital form. SigiDoc is intended for both
                the creation of digital-born editions as well as digital conversion of paper
                publications and has been conceived to provide the users with a common basis for
                developing their projects and to give them the freedom to customise their
                approach.</p>
              <p>SigiDoc is largely based on the ongoing experience of EpiDoc and aims at becoming
                the standard tool for the spreading of digital sigillography while delivering a
                standard for the digital encoding of Byzantine seals. </p>
              <p>GitHub repository available <a href="https://github.com/SigiDoc/SigiDoc" target="_blank">here</a>.</p>
            </div>
          </div>
        </div>
      </main>
    </kiln:block>
  </kiln:child>
</kiln:root>
